Guide to the Barbara Guest Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1953-2004; Series II
  - Writings by Guest
    - Poetry
      - Chalk, undated (Box 51, Folder 1009)
        Copy of poems from printed book [collection, not single poem]
      - The Chicken Coop, undated (Box 51, Folder 1010)
      - Choice, undated (Box 51, Folder 1011)
      - Circassians, undated (Box 52, Folder 1012)
      - The Classical Clock, undated (Box 52, Folder 1013)
      - Cleopatra's Needle, undated (Box 52, Folder 1014)
      - Cloud-Life with Honey, undated (Box 52, Folder 1015)
      - Clouds Near the Windmill, 1963 August (Box 52, Folder 1016)
        1 autograph manuscript; 3 typescripts, corrected [titled "The Clouds" in one version]
      - Collected Poems and Library of Congress permission to record; "Heroic Stages" (rewritten 2/28/2002), 1962- (Box 52, Folder 1017)
      - Colonial Hours, undated (Box 52, Folder 1018)
        1 autograph manuscript; 2 typescript, corrected
      - Complaint, undated (Box 52, Folder 1019)
      - Compulsive Stairs, undated (Box 52, Folder 1020)
      - Concertina, undated (Box 52, Folder 1021)
      - Confession of my Images, undated (Box 52, Folder 1022)
      - Configuration, undated (Box 52, Folder 1023)
      - Consonants, undated (Box 52, Folder 1024)
      - Constabul's Method, undated (Box 52, Folder 1025)
        1 typescript; includes correspondence with "Brian"
      - The Costs, undated (Box 52, Folder 1026)
      - The Countess from Minneapolis, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 1027-1030)
        Many typescript, corrected; several autograph manuscripts; copy of poems from printed book; enclosures (2 empty postcards, newspaper clipping) [collection, not single poem]
      - Credo in Mortibus, undated (Box 52, Folder 1031)
        1 typescript, corrected [cf. "Beta in Greek"]
      - The Crisis, undated (Box 52, Folder 1032)
      - Cropped Turf, undated (Box 52, Folder 1033)
      - Dark Rhyming, undated (Box 52, Folder 1034)
      - Days, undated (Box 52, Folder 1035)
        3 typescripts
      - A Day You Encountered an Intruder, undated (Box 52, Folder 1036)
      - Defensive Rapture, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 1037-1039)
        Many typescripts, corrected; copies from printed book; galley proofs; enclosures (check and lists) [collection, not single poem]
      - Defensive Rapture, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1040-1048)
      - Direction, undated (Box 53, Folder 1049)
      - Dissonance Royal Traveler, undated (Box 53, Folder 1050)
      - Divergence, undated (Box 53, Folder 1051)
        1 autograph manuscripts
      - Door Bells, 1970 May (Box 53, Folder 1052)
      - The Doorman's Whistle, undated (Box 53, Folder 1053)
      - Dora Maar, undated (Box 53, Folder 1054)
      - Doubleness, undated (Box 53, Folder 1055)
        Several typescript
      - Drawing a Blank, 1972 February 16 (Box 53, Folder 1056)
      - E, undated (Box 54, Folder 1057)
      - Early Music, undated (Box 54, Folder 1058)
      - East of Omsk, 1967 February (Box 54, Folder 1059)
      - Eating Chocolate Ice Cream: Reading Mayakovsky, undated (Box 54, Folder 1060)
      - Effervescence, undated (Box 54, Folder 1061)
      - Egypt, 1971 April (Box 54, Folder 1062)
      - ELF, undated (Box 54, Folder 1063)
        1 typescript, printout
      - An Emphasis Falls on Reality, undated (Box 54, Folder 1064)
        Several typescripts
      - Epitaph, undated (Box 54, Folder 1065)
      - Eugene Alexander Anton, undated (Box 54, Folder 1066)
        1 autograph manuscript; 2 typescripts [autograph manuscript version entitled "Eugene Alexander Yuri"]
      - Evening, undated (Box 54, Folder 1067)
        1 handwritten; 1 typescript
      - Even Ovid, 1970 February (Box 54, Folder 1068)
      - Everything in the Air Is a Bird, undated (Box 54, Folder 1069)
      - An Excursion, undated (Box 54, Folder 1070)
      - Fair Realism, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 1071-1076)
        Many typescript, corrected; copies from printed book; proofs [collection, not single poem]
      - Fan Poems, undated (Box 55, Folder 1077)
      - The Fatherless Poem, undated (Box 55, Folder 1078)
      - The Fault of Art, 1964 April (Box 55, Folder 1079)
        1 autograph manuscript; 2 typescripts, corrected
      - Fear Longing, undated (Box 55, Folder 1080)
      - Finally, to the Italian Girl, undated (Box 55, Folder 1081)
      - Finnish Opera, undated (Box 55, Folder 1082)
      - First Prints of Green, undated (Box 55, Folder 1083)
      - Fit Für Gaing Farth, undated (Box 55, Folder 1084)
      - The Flaking Ceiling, undated (Box 55, Folder 1085)
      - Flemish Reprint, undated (Box 55, Folder 1086)
      - Florida, undated (Box 55, Folder 1087)
      - Folk Song, undated (Box 55, Folder 1088)
      - Footfall, undated (Box 55, Folder 1089)
      - Forced Exit, 1993 October (Box 55, Folder 1090)
        1 autograph manuscripts; 1 typescript, corrected
      - Foreheads, undated (Box 55, Folder 1091)
        1 typescript (superimposed segmentation by hand)
      - A Form of Protest Against the Anonymity of Mass Production in the Technological Civilization, undated (Box 55, Folder 1092)
      - Four Moroccan Studies, undated (Box 55, Folder 1093)
        1 autograph manuscript (on back of another typescript poem); 2 typescripts
      - From the North, undated (Box 55, Folder 1094)
      - The Frost, undated (Box 55, Folder 1095)
        1 typescript (notes by hand)
      - A Garment, undated (Box 55, Folder 1096)
        2 typescripts, corrected [1 version called just "Garment"]
      - Geese Blood, undated (Box 55, Folder 1097)
      - Geography, 1962 January 19 (Box 55, Folder 1098)
      - George Sand, undated (Box 55, Folder 1099)
        1 autograph manuscript 2 typescripts
      - Ghosts, 1998 April–1998 June (Box 55, Folder 1100)
      - The Glass Mountain, undated (Box 55, Folder 1101)
      - Glimpses of Toledo, undated (Box 55, Folder 1102)
      - Going to the Movies with Fay, undated (Box 55, Folder 1103)
      - Grantmakers in the Arts Reader, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 1104)
        Printed magazine [Guest's poem "Green Shoots" is on p. 38]
      - Gravel, undated (Box 55, Folder 1105)
        1 autograph manuscript; 3 typescripts (2 are corrected)
      - The Green Fly, undated (Box 55, Folder 1106)
      - H.D., 2004 (Box 55, Folder 1107-1108)
        1 typescript and printed
      - Half-Kennings, undated (Box 55, Folder 1109)
      - Handbook of Surfing, undated (Box 55, Folder 1110)
      - Hands, undated (Box 55, Folder 1111)
      - Heat, undated (Box 55, Folder 1112)
      - Her Face: Not Her Face, undated (Box 55, Folder 1113)
      - Histoire, undated (Box 55, Folder 1114)
      - Hohenzollern, undated (Box 55, Folder 1115)
      - Homage, undated (Box 55, Folder 1116)
      - How Far It Doth Climb, undated (Box 55, Folder 1117)
      - The Hudson River, undated (Box 55, Folder 1118)
      - If So, undated (Box 55, Folder 1119)
      - If So, Tell Me, 1998 April–1999 April (Box 56, Folder 1120-1123)
        Many typescripts, corrected; several handwritten [collection, not single poem; one folder also contains "Rocks on a Platter"]
      - I Have Lost Everything, undated (Box 56, Folder 1124)
      - Ilex, undated (Box 56, Folder 1125)
        Several autograph manuscripts; several typescripts, corrected
      - Illicit Love, undated (Box 56, Folder 1126)
      - Illyria, 1970 March–1970 May (Box 56, Folder 1127)
      - Il Splash, 1998 July 30 (Box 56, Folder 1128-1130)
        Many typescripts, corrected; proofs (also contains "Airborne and "Reverie of the Making of a Poem" and "Lily") [collection, not single poem]
      - I'm the Marble, 1984 July (Box 56, Folder 1131)
      - Indira!, undated (Box 56, Folder 1132)
      - In the Hotel, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 1133)
      - In Memory, undated (Box 56, Folder 1134)
      - In Memory of Brancusi, undated (Box 56, Folder 1135)
      - In the Museum, undated (Box 56, Folder 1136)
      - Itinerary, undated (Box 56, Folder 1137)
      - Jean Arp, undated (Box 56, Folder 1138)
      - Joanna the Mad: Philip the Bold, undated (Box 56, Folder 1139)
      - July Again, undated (Box 56, Folder 1140)
        1 typescript (on back of another handwritten poem)
      - Knight of the Swan, undated (Box 56, Folder 1141)
      - K'un; Ch'ien, undated (Box 56, Folder 1142)
      - Landscape, undated (Box 57, Folder 1143)
        2 autograph manuscript; 1 typescript, corrected
      - Leaning Structures, undated (Box 57, Folder 1144)
      - Leaving Modernity, undated (Box 57, Folder 1145)
      - Letter to my Mother, undated (Box 57, Folder 1146)
      - Lexicon Trues, undated (Box 57, Folder 1147)
      - Lit Dusk, undated (Box 57, Folder 1148)
      - The Location of Things, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 1149-1151)
      - A Long Time, undated (Box 57, Folder 1152)
      - Looking at Flowers Through Tears, undated (Box 57, Folder 1153)
        1 autograph manuscript; 3 typescripts, corrected
      - Lost Speech, undated (Box 57, Folder 1154)
        Several typescripts [1 entitled "The Lost Speech"]
      - The Luminous, 1999 March (Box 57, Folder 1155)
        Handmade book
      - Lunch at Helen Frankenthaler's, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 1156)
      - Mahogany Delight, undated (Box 57, Folder 1157)
      - Mary Wollstonecraft, undated (Box 57, Folder 1158)
      - Memory. Pale Chloroform., undated (Box 57, Folder 1159)
      - Meowing, undated (Box 57, Folder 1160)
      - Miniatures and Other Poems, 2001–2002 (Box 57, Folder 1161-1164)
        Many typescripts, corrected; proofs; enclosure (proposed cover) [collection, not single poem]
      - Miniatures and Other Poems, 2001–2002 (Box 58, Folder 1165-1171)
      - Mi Scusi, undated (Box 58, Folder 1172)
        1 handwritten; 2 typescripts, corrected
      - A Mistake the Size of an Eyelash, undated (Box 58, Folder 1173)
      - Monograms, undated (Box 58, Folder 1174)
      - Moscow Mansions, 1970 September 8–1973 (Box 58, Folder 1175-1180)
        Many typescripts; proofs; enclosures (related correspondence, notes)
      - Mountains of Glass, undated (Box 59, Folder 1181)
      - Multiplicity, undated (Box 59, Folder 1182)
      - Museum, undated (Box 59, Folder 1183)
      - Music History, undated (Box 59, Folder 1184)
      - Musicality, undated (Box 59, Folder 1185)
        Mock-up with letter from Rena Rosenwasser
      - The Nail Driven Into Smoke, undated (Box 59, Folder 1186)
      - Nankuu, undated (Box 59, Folder 1187)
      - Nebraska, 1970 October (Box 59, Folder 1188)
      - New Hampshire, 1971 April (Box 59, Folder 1189)
      - La Noche Entra en Calor, undated (Box 59, Folder 1190)
        Several typescripts [1 entitled "La Noche Entra con Color"]
      - Nodes, undated (Box 59, Folder 1191)
        2 typescripts; autograph manuscript material
      - Non Est…, undated (Box 59, Folder 1192)
      - Nordic Interlude, undated (Box 59, Folder 1193)
      - Nostalgia of the Infinite, 2002 February 11 (Box 59, Folder 1194-1195)
        Several typescripts; enclosure (De Chirico painting of same title) [collection, not single poem]
      - Nouveaux Huevos, 2000 (Box 59, Folder 1196)
        3 fliers
      - The Nude, undated (Box 59, Folder 1197)
      - On the Peaches of Larks (Robbers), 1970 February (Box 59, Folder 1198)
      - Ojjiba, undated (Box 59, Folder 1199)
      - The Old Silk Road, undated (Box 59, Folder 1200)
      - Olivetti Ode, 1962 December (Box 59, Folder 1201)
        1 autograph manuscript; 1 typescript [autograph manuscript version entitled "Olivetti Olivetti"]
      - On a Chinese Vase, 1963 January (Box 59, Folder 1202)
      - On the Road to Rome, undated (Box 59, Folder 1203)
      - On the Verge of the Path, undated (Box 59, Folder 1204)
      - On Wickabogue Road, undated (Box 59, Folder 1205)
      - The Open Skies, undated (Box 59, Folder 1206)
        1 autograph manuscript; 1 typescript, corrected
      - Opposites, undated (Box 59, Folder 1207)
      - O Restless Suspicion, undated (Box 59, Folder 1208)
      - Otranto, undated (Box 59, Folder 1209)
      - Outside of This, That Is, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1210)
        2 printed books
      - Owl Ode, undated (Box 59, Folder 1211)
        1 autograph manuscript; 2 typescripts [handwritten version entitled "Owl Poem"]
      - Palazzo Kebs und waffeln, undated (Box 59, Folder 1212)
        1 autograph manuscript [second word of title uncertain]
      - Parachutes, My Love, Could Carry Us Higher, 2002 January 27 (Box 59, Folder 1213-1214)
        Typescript and printed versions with printout photograph of printed poem
      - Parade's End, 1963 November (Box 59, Folder 1215)
      - Passage, undated (Box 59, Folder 1216)
      - Pathos, undated (Box 59, Folder 1217-1219)
        Many typescripts, corrected [1 folder also contains "Blurred Edge"]
      - The Paws, 1965 February (Box 60, Folder 1220)
      - Perspectus, undated (Box 60, Folder 1221)
      - Phenomena, undated (Box 60, Folder 1222)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 60, Folder 1223)
      - Pity, undated (Box 60, Folder 1224)
      - The Pleiades, undated (Box 60, Folder 1225)
        Many typescripts, corrected
      - Poem, undated (Box 60, Folder 1226)
      - Poems, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 1227-1229)
        Copies of poems from printed book [book contained "The Location of Things," "Archaics," "The Open Skies"]
      - PoemScape, undated (Box 60, Folder 1230)
      - The Poet Who Threw Roses, undated (Box 60, Folder 1231-1232)
        Copy of poem from printed book; many typescripts, corrected
      - Poetry Scenes & Discord, undated (Box 60, Folder 1233)
      - Points, undated (Box 60, Folder 1234)
      - "Poor Trieste", undated (Box 60, Folder 1235)
      - Postoffice Wisdom, undated (Box 60, Folder 1236)
      - Prague Music, undated (Box 60, Folder 1237)
      - Prayer for Antoninius (en route to San Francisco), undated (Box 60, Folder 1238)
      - Prefaces, undated (Box 60, Folder 1239)
      - Prelude, undated (Box 60, Folder 1240)
      - El Problema, undated (Box 60, Folder 1241)
      - Psyche, undated (Box 60, Folder 1242)
      - Quiet, undated (Box 60, Folder 1243)
      - Quill, Solitary Apparition, 1996 (Box 60, Folder 1244-1249)
        Many typescripts, corrected; galley proofs; prototype cover [collection, not single poem]
      - Quilts
        - Drafts, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1250)
        - Proofs, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1251)
        - Final proof, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1252)
        - Assorted notes and drafts, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1253)
        - Xeroxes of printed version, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1254)
        - Cover collage art by Deborah Friedman, undated (Box 61, Folder 1255-1258)
        - Receipts, undated (Box 61, Folder 1259-1260)
        - Assorted sheets of final printing, incomplete, undated (Box 61, Folder 1261)
        - Quilts: an exhibit of books at Windows on White, undated (Box 61, Folder 1262)
          Includes photographs, printed material, and art work
        - Printed versions, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1263-1267)
      - Raddle Moon, 1999 June 9–1999 August 13 (Box 63, Folder 1269)
        Cover page; galley proofs; many typescripts, corrected; enclosure (letter) [collection, not single poem]
      - Rags, undated (Box 63, Folder 1270)
      - A Reason, undated (Box 63, Folder 1271)
      - Red Dye, undated (Box 63, Folder 1272)
      - The Red Gaze, 2003–2004 (Box 63, Folder 1273-1274)
        Many typescripts, corrected; enclosures (bound booklet, emails, printout of website) [collection, not single poem]
      - Red Lilies, 1972 February 14 (Box 63, Folder 1275)
      - The Rest of the Day, undated (Box 63, Folder 1276)
      - The Return of the Muses, 1963 April 4 (Box 63, Folder 1277)
        1 autograph manuscript several typescripts [collection, not single poem]
      - A Reverie on the Making of a Poem, 1998- (Box 63, Folder 1278)
      - Revolution and Lullaby, undated (Box 63, Folder 1279)
      - Rivers, undated (Box 63, Folder 1280)
      - The Rose Marble Tree, undated (Box 64, Folder 1281)
      - Roses, 1963 October 14 (Box 64, Folder 1282)
      - Rosy Ensconcements, 1970 February (Box 64, Folder 1283)
      - Sangre, undated (Box 64, Folder 1284)
      - Saving Tallow, undated (Box 64, Folder 1285)
      - Sassafras, undated (Box 64, Folder 1286)
      - Savon Pompeia, undated (Box 64, Folder 1287)
      - The School of Madame Mordkin, 1957 November (Box 64, Folder 1288)
      - The Screen of Distance and Other Poems, undated (Box 64, Folder 1289)
        Proof [collection, not single poem]
      - See Song, undated (Box 64, Folder 1290)
      - Selected Poems, 1995 January 18–1995 February 6 (Box 64, Folder 1291)
        Bound proofs; enclosures (2 letters) [collection, not single poem]
      - Semi Kennings, undated (Box 64, Folder 1292)
      - Send Me a Telegram, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 1293)
        2 broadside, corrected; 2 typescripts
      - Sensitivity, undated (Box 64, Folder 1294)
      - Separation, undated (Box 65, Folder 1295)
      - Settimana della Poesia, undated (Box 65, Folder 1296)
      - Sharawadgi, undated (Box 65, Folder 1297)
      - She Considers with Awe, undated (Box 65, Folder 1298)
      - Shelley Portfolio, undated (Box 65, Folder 1299)
      - Shifting Atmosphere, undated (Box 65, Folder 1300)
        Several typescripts [titled "Alternative Atmospheres" in one version]
      - Shifting the Iris, undated (Box 65, Folder 1301)
      - Shifting Persona, undated (Box 65, Folder 1302)
        1 typescript, corrected [should probably be classified as prose]
      - Shuffling Light, undated (Box 65, Folder 1303)
      - Silk, undated (Box 65, Folder 1304)
      - Sleeping Beauty, undated (Box 65, Folder 1305)
        1 autograph manuscript; several typescripts, corrected
      - [Soft Dissonance], undated (Box 65, Folder 1306)
        1 typescript, corrected [title whited-out]
      - The Speech Spoon, undated (Box 65, Folder 1307)
        Several typescripts, corrected [same poem as "Velvet Monkey"]
      - Startling Maneuvers, undated (Box 65, Folder 1308)
        1 typescript; enclosure (Post-It with phone number)
      - Storm Poem, 1964 September (Box 65, Folder 1309)
      - Storytelling, undated (Box 65, Folder 1310)
      - The Stragglers, undated (Box 65, Folder 1311)
      - Strings, undated (Box 65, Folder 1312)
      - Stripped Tales, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 1313-1316)
        Proofs; many typescripts, corrected; broadsides [collection, not single poem]
      - The Strum, undated (Box 65, Folder 1317)
      - Stupid Physical Pain, 1971 September (Box 65, Folder 1318)
      - Submission, undated (Box 65, Folder 1319)
      - Summon Song, undated (Box 62, Folder 1268)
      - Surfing, 1966 May (Box 65, Folder 1320)
        2 typescripts; 1 galley proof
      - Symbiosis, undated (Box 66, Folder 1321-1326)
        Many typescripts, corrected; bound book
      - Taking a Bath While Snow Is Falling, undated (Box 66, Folder 1327)
      - This Innocent Song, undated (Box 66, Folder 1328)
      - This Way to Pity, undated (Box 66, Folder 1329)
      - The Thread, undated (Box 66, Folder 1330)
      - Tiny Foreign Tears, undated (Box 66, Folder 1331)
        3 typescripts, corrected [title changed to just "Foreign Tears" in one version]
      - Transcription, undated (Box 66, Folder 1332)
      - Turkey Villas, undated (Box 66, Folder 1333)
      - The Türler Losses, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1334-1336)
        Many typescripts, corrected; proofs; copies of poems from printed book [one folder also contains "Bioraphy" and "Quilts"]
      - Twenty, undated (Box 67, Folder 1337)
      - Unusual Figures, undated (Box 67, Folder 1338)
      - Urban Movements, undated (Box 67, Folder 1339)
      - Valorous Vine, undated (Box 67, Folder 1340-1341)
        Many typescripts, corrected [also contains other poems from "If So, Tell Me"]
      - Valuable Mörike, undated (Box 67, Folder 1342)
      - Velvet Monkey, undated (Box 67, Folder 1343)
        1 typescript [see "The Speech Spoon, above]
      - Verba in Memoriam, undated (Box 67, Folder 1344)
      - The View from Kandinsky's Window, undated (Box 67, Folder 1345)
      - Voice, undated (Box 67, Folder 1346)
      - Walking Away, 1966 February (Box 67, Folder 1347)
      - Walking Buddha, undated (Box 67, Folder 1348)
      - The Watering Can, 1964 February (Box 67, Folder 1349)
      - Water Kingdoms, undated (Box 67, Folder 1350)
      - A Way of Being, 1963 August (Box 67, Folder 1351)
      - Wells Fargo, undated (Box 67, Folder 1352)
      - Western Additives, undated (Box 67, Folder 1353)
      - Wet Birds on Sunday, undated (Box 67, Folder 1354)
      - What Inspires Me, undated (Box 67, Folder 1355)
      - The Wild Garden Overlooked by Night Lights, undated (Box 67, Folder 1356)
      - Wool Gathering, undated (Box 67, Folder 1357)
      - Your Poems, undated (Box 67, Folder 1358)
      - Zodiac Dark, undated (Box 67, Folder 1359)
      - Drafts, 1952-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1360)
        Typescripts
      - Drafts, 1953-1961 (poetry) (Box 67, Folder 1361)
      - Drafts, 1958-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1362)
      - Drafts, 1961-1969 (Box 68, Folder 1363)
      - Drafts 1965-1970 (Box 68, Folder 1364)
      - Drafts, 1973-1977 (Box 68, Folder 1365)
      - Drafts 1 of 3, 1976-1978 (Box 68, Folder 1366)
        Autograph manuscripts and typescripts; enclosures (includes newspaper clipping, envelopes)
      - Drafts 2 of 3, undated (Box 68, Folder 1367)
        Autograph manuscripts and typescripts
      - Drafts 3 of 3, undated (Box 68, Folder 1368)
      - Drafts, 1982-1983 (Box 68, Folder 1369)
      - Drafts, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 68, Folder 1369a)
      - Drafts, 1980–1989 (Box 69, Folder 1370-1370j)
      - Drafts, undated (Box 70, Folder 1371-1376)
        1 typescript; enclosures (includes photographs, postcard, newspaper clippings, fliers)
      - Drafts, undated (Box 71, Folder 1377)
      - Drafts of poems and a notepad, undated (Box 71, Folder 1378)
      - Poetry, undated (Box 71, Folder 1379-1386)
      - Drafts, including some prose, undated (Box 71, Folder 1387)
      - Unsorted poetry drafts and papers, undated (Box 72, Folder 1388-1395)
      - Unsorted poetry drafts and papers, undated (Box 73, Folder 1396-1403)
      - Unsorted poetry drafts and papers, undated (Box 74, Folder 1404-1408)
      - Unsorted poetry drafts and papers, undated (Box 75, Folder 1409-1410)
    - Prose
      - "Carolina Moon", 1957 (Box 76, Folder 1411)
        1 typescript; enclosure (envelope)
      - The Confetti Trees: Motion Picture Stories, undated (Box 76, Folder 1411a-1411d)
      - Rocks on a Platter: Notes on Literature, 1996–1999 (Box 156, Folder 2038-2044)
        Many typescripts, corrected; galley proofs; enclosures (letter from the editor, related papers) [one folder also contains "The Confetti Trees"; another contains poems from "If So, Tell Me"]
      - Seeking Air, 1975–1978 (Box 76, Folder 1412-1413)
        1 typescript, corrected; enclosures (includes correspondence, notebook, newspaper clippings)
      - Seeking Air, 1975–1978 (Box 77, Folder 1414-1418)
      - Seeking Air, 1975–1978 (Box 78, Folder 1419-1420)
      - "Stripped Tales", undated (Box 78, Folder 1421-1423)
        1 typescript (corrected, includes 1 bound version)
      - "The White Alsatian", 1957 (Box 78, Folder 1424)
      - Drafts, undated (Box 79, Folder 1425-1426)
        1 typescript; letters; magazine; etc., includes poetry
    - Drama
      - "Chinese Ghost Restaurant", undated (Box 80, Folder 1427-1428)
        1 typescript; bound book by Anne Slacik and Norma Cole
      - "Cremorne Gardens", 1965 (Box 80, Folder 1429)
        1 typescript; enclosure (booklet) [also includes "Port"]
      - "The Diving Board", undated (Box 80, Folder 1430)
        1 typescript [also includes "The Heart Attack" and "Chinese Ghost Restaurant"]
      - "The Execution of Mary Stewart", undated (Box 80, Folder 1431-1435)